Once upon a time... can happen any time.
A Cinderella Story is a comedy, family, romance film directed by Mark Rosman.
Routinely exploited by her wicked stepmother, the downtrodden Samantha Montgomery is excited
about the prospect of meeting her Internet beau at the school's Halloween dance.
Sam Montgomery, played by Hilary Duff.
Austin Ames, played by Chad Michael Murray.
Fiona, played by Jennifer Coolidge.
Carter Farrell, played by Dan Byrd.
Rhonda, played by Regina King.
Shelby Cummings, played by Julie Gonzalo.
A Cinderella Story is a 2004 American teen romantic comedy film directed by Mark Rosman, written by Leigh
Dunlap and starring Hilary Duff, Chad Michael Murray, Jennifer Coolidge, and Regina King.
A modernization of the classic Cinderella folklore, the film's plot revolves around two
internet pen pals who plan to meet in person at their high school's Halloween dance.
The film was released on July 16, 2004, and grossed $70.1
million against its $19 million budget.
It inspired multiple straight-to-video films.
Over the years, it has developed into a cult classic.
The film explores themes of high school, work,
jealousy, american football, stepmother.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.